{
  "english": [
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Elephant",
      "rightAnswer": "elefant",
      "wrongAnswer": ["lejon", "krokodil", "antilop"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Tiger",
      "rightAnswer": "tiger",
      "wrongAnswer": ["björn", "hund", "katt"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Giraffe",
      "rightAnswer": "giraff",
      "wrongAnswer": ["noshörning", "elefant", "apa"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    { 
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Monkey",
      "rightAnswer": "apa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["elefant", "katt", "fågel"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Lion", 
      "rightAnswer": "lejon",
      "wrongAnswer": [ "tiger", "elefant", "häst"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Zebra", 
      "rightAnswer": "zebra", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["giraff", "elefant", "ko"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Dolphin",
      "rightAnswer": "delfin",
      "wrongAnswer": [ "val", "haj", "fisk"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Penguin",
      "rightAnswer": "pingvin",
      "wrongAnswer": ["elefant", "papegoja", "fågel"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Kangaroo",
      "rightAnswer": "känguru",
      "wrongAnswer": [ "koala", "elefant", "lejon"],
      "category": "animals"
    },
    { 
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Eagle",
      "rightAnswer": "örn", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["falk", "fladdermus", "fisk"],
      "category": "animals" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Blue", 
      "rightAnswer": "blå", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["gul", "röd", "grön"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Green", 
      "rightAnswer": "grön", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["blå", "rosa", "svart"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Red",
      "rightAnswer": "röd", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["gul", "blå", "lila"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Yellow",
      "rightAnswer": "gul", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["blå", "röd", "vit"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Purple",
      "rightAnswer": "lila",
      "wrongAnswer": ["orange", "grön", "rosa"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Orange", 
      "rightAnswer": "orange", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["röd", "gul", "brun"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Pink", 
      "rightAnswer":"rosa", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["lila", "blå", "grön"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Brown", 
      "rightAnswer": "brun", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["grön", "röd", "gul"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Black", 
      "rightAnswer": "svart", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["vit", "blå", "grå"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "White", 
      "rightAnswer": "vit", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["svart", "brun", "grön"],
      "category": "colors" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Football",
      "rightAnswer": "fotboll", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["hockey", "basket", "tennis"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Basketball",
      "rightAnswer": "basket", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["fotboll", "simning", "golf"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Tennis",
      "rightAnswer": "tennis", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["fotboll", "bordtennis", "volleyboll"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Swimming",
      "rightAnswer": "simning", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["löpning", "cykling", "basket"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Running",
      "rightAnswer": "löpning", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["simning", "cykling", "basket"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Cycling",
      "rightAnswer": "cykling",
      "wrongAnswer": ["simning", "löpning", "fotboll"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Volleyball",
      "rightAnswer": "volleyboll", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["fotboll", "basket", "tennis"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Golf", 
      "rightAnswer": "golf", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["tennis", "fotboll", "basket"],
      "category": "sports" 
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Hockey",
      "rightAnswer": "ishockey", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["fotboll", "basket", "tennis"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Skiing",
      "rightAnswer": "skidåkning", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["simning", "löpning", "cykling"],
      "category": "sports"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Doctor",
      "rightAnswer": "läkare", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["lärare", "kock", "servitör"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Teacher",
      "rightAnswer": "lärare", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "servitör", "kock"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Engineer",
      "rightAnswer": "ingenjör", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "advokat", "tandläkare"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    { 
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Chef", 
      "rightAnswer": "kock", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "servitör", "lärare"],
      "category": "occupations" 
    },
    { 
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Pilot", 
      "rightAnswer": "pilot", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "brandman", "polis"],
      "category": "occupations" 
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Lawyer",
      "rightAnswer": "advokat", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "ingenjör", "tandläkare"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Nurse",
      "rightAnswer": "sjuksköterska", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "lärare", "kock"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Artist",
      "rightAnswer": "konstnär", 
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "ingenjör", "advokat"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Firefighter",
      "rightAnswer": "brandman",
      "wrongAnswer": ["pilot", "läkare", "polis"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Police officer",
      "rightAnswer": "polis",
      "wrongAnswer": ["läkare", "kock", "servitör"],
      "category": "occupations"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Skirt",
      "rightAnswer": "kjol",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skjorta", "sko", "klänning"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Shoe",
      "rightAnswer": "sko",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hatt", "väska", "scarf"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Trousers",
      "rightAnswer": "byxor",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skor", "vantar", "tröja"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Dress",
      "rightAnswer": "klänning",
      "wrongAnswer": ["tröja", "byxor", "kjol"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Bag",
      "rightAnswer": "väska",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hatt", "sko", "kofta"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Boots",
      "rightAnswer": "stövlar",
      "wrongAnswer": ["byxor", "sandaler", "tröja"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Coat",
      "rightAnswer": "kappa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["kostym", "väst", "klänning"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Suit",
      "rightAnswer": "kostym",
      "wrongAnswer": ["kappa", "skjorta", "kjol"],
      "category": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Apple",
      "rightAnswer": "äpple",
      "wrongAnswer": ["päron", "banan", "apelsin"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Pear",
      "rightAnswer": "päron",
      "wrongAnswer": ["äpple", "vindruva", "apelsin"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Orange",
      "rightAnswer": "apelsin",
      "wrongAnswer": ["äpple", "melon", "citron"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Lemon",
      "rightAnswer": "citron",
      "wrongAnswer": ["apelsin", "äpple", "melon"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Cucumber",
      "rightAnswer": "gurka",
      "wrongAnswer": ["tomat", "citron", "morot"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Carrot",
      "rightAnswer": "morot",
      "wrongAnswer": ["citron", "gurka", "tomat"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Potato",
      "rightAnswer": "potatis",
      "wrongAnswer": ["tomat", "päron", "morot"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Tomato",
      "rightAnswer": "tomat",
      "wrongAnswer": ["morot", "potatis", "paprika"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Lettuce",
      "rightAnswer": "sallad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["lök", "morot", "paprika"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Onion",
      "rightAnswer": "lök",
      "wrongAnswer": ["gurka", "tomat", "blomkål"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Garlic",
      "rightAnswer": "vitlök",
      "wrongAnswer": ["grönkål", "sparris", "paprika"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Asparagus",
      "rightAnswer": "sparris",
      "wrongAnswer": ["paprika", "majs", "tomat"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Corn",
      "rightAnswer": "majs",
      "wrongAnswer": ["kål", "lök", "morot"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Sandwich",
      "rightAnswer": "smörgås",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hamburgare", "sallad", "korv"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Mushroom",
      "rightAnswer": "svamp",
      "wrongAnswer": ["morot", "sparris", "lök"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Sausage",
      "rightAnswer": "korv",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sås", "sallad", "smörgås"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Coffee",
      "rightAnswer": "kaffe",
      "wrongAnswer": ["te", "läsk", "mjölk"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Soda",
      "rightAnswer": "läsk",
      "wrongAnswer": ["mjölk", "kaffe", "saft"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Milk",
      "rightAnswer": "mjölk",
      "wrongAnswer": ["saft", "läsk", "grädde"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Cream",
      "rightAnswer": "grädde",
      "wrongAnswer": ["mjölk", "yoghurt", "juice"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Sugar",
      "rightAnswer": "socker",
      "wrongAnswer": ["salt", "peppar", "mjöl"],
      "category": "food"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Pen",
      "rightAnswer": "penna",
      "wrongAnswer": ["krita", "suddgummi", "pensel"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Crayon",
      "rightAnswer": "krita",
      "wrongAnswer": ["penna", "pensel", "suddgummi"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Eraser",
      "rightAnswer": "suddgummi",
      "wrongAnswer": ["penna", "pensel", "linjal"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Ruler",
      "rightAnswer": "linjal",
      "wrongAnswer": ["suddgummi", "penna", "krita"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Paper",
      "rightAnswer": "papper",
      "wrongAnswer": ["penna", "pensel", "bok"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Table",
      "rightAnswer": "bord",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "soffa", "hylla"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Couch",
      "rightAnswer": "soffa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "bord", "hylla"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Chair",
      "rightAnswer": "stol",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hylla", "bord", "soffa"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Shelf",
      "rightAnswer": "hylla",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "soffa", "bord"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Airplane",
      "rightAnswer": "flygplan",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "tåg", "båt"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Car",
      "rightAnswer": "bil",
      "wrongAnswer": ["flygplan", "tåg", "båt"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Train",
      "rightAnswer": "tåg",
      "wrongAnswer": ["flygplan", "båt", "bil"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Boat",
      "rightAnswer": "båt",
      "wrongAnswer": ["flygplan", "bil", "tåg"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "House",
      "rightAnswer": "hus",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skola", "kyrka", "sjukhus"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "School",
      "rightAnswer": "skola",
      "wrongAnswer": ["kyrka", "sjukhus", "hus"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Church",
      "rightAnswer": "kyrka",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sjukhus", "hus", "skola"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Hospital",
      "rightAnswer": "Sjukhus",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hus", "skola", "kyrka"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Summer",
      "rightAnswer": "sommar",
      "wrongAnswer": ["vår", "höst", "vinter"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Winter",
      "rightAnswer": "vinter",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sommar", "vår", "höst"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Spring",
      "rightAnswer": "vår",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sommar", "höst", "vinter"],
      "category": "objects"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Autumn",
      "rightAnswer": "höst",
      "wrongAnswer": ["vinter", "sommar", "vår"],
      "category": "objects"
    }
  ]
}
